Over a decade ago,
the famous Huo Sanlang,
rumored to be the reincarnation of the Fire God.
It was nothing but a cheap trick.
Last night at midnight,
where were you?
I was in Wuyou City.
I have been staying in Wuyou City for over a decade,
until today,
when you captured me and brought me here.
We should find a chance to see
if this Huo Sanlang can be used
by my Bingjingwu.
My Lord,
he is just an old man who has been in Wuyou City for over a decade.
Shut up!
With his marvelous fire escape technique,
ten of you can't compare to him.
My Lord,
Uncle Chai is already enough trouble.
Are we going to add another prisoner from Wuyou City?
You are the one who attacked me
at the cave entrance that day, right?
I smell a strong scent of dogs on you.
You keep dogs, don't you?
Actually,
I've seen you and your dogs
a long time ago.
My name is Meng Qian,
making a living at Sangjia Wazi.
For those dogs, you used to
fight against the officials frequently.
Your name is Qi Si, right?
You can understand human language, right?
If you understand me,
just nod.
Actually,
we are the same kind of people.
You have dogs to take care of.
I have a sister-in-law and a younger sister to take care of.
My sister is seriously ill.
The people who could call my name
are all gone.
Then
I'll call you
Brother Qisi.
Just call me Chaijiu.
Okay,
Brother Chaijiu.
Did you hear that just now?
Someone...
Someone from above wants to let us go.
It's all because of that Official Chu.
Her?
Feigning compliance,
she won't be an official for much longer.
Let's find a chance later.
How about that?
Where can I go?
You...
don't you want freedom?
Just like before.
My Lord.
About releasing the prisoner,
Duke Zhou only gave us two hours.
Time is almost up.
Release the prisoner?
What prisoner?
Who in Bingjingwu needs to be released?
As for Liu Heizi,
continue the interrogation
until he confesses.
What about Zhu Zitong?
I will give him a new identity.
My man
does not need to be released.
What?
Don't you understand?
He is my man from Bingjingwu.
And the idler?
He is still useful.
Wait until Lord Zhou's men come back,
then we will see.
Sister,
I was just about to go looking for you.
How could I bear to make you tire yourself out?
The Lantern Festival is approaching.
Dongjing City is full of all sorts of people right now,
making it extremely unsafe.
I am truly worried about you.
Was that letter
helpful to you, Sister?
The word 'Liangshan' you deduced from the secret letter
must be true.
I have already encountered those thieves in Wuyou City.
Sister,
you actually went to Wuyou City?
Yes.
Beneath Dongjing City,
there is indeed a whole other world.
And Wuyou City
is indeed very dangerous.
But how did those Liangshan thieves
find Wuyou City so easily?
They found an idler.
That man is familiar with the geography of Dongjing.
He is called something like
the Geography Ghost of Dongjing.
There is such a person?
There are indeed many capable and strange people in Dongjing.
Although you
are physically weak,
your wisdom and talent
are also exceptionally good, aren't they?
I don't even know
how to answer that, Sister.
However,
I would like to meet that idler.
He is still in my ice prison right now.
I always feel
that he hasn't confessed the whole truth yet.
What do you
want to do, Sister?
I ordered someone to bring his sister-in-law and sister here.
Let's see if he confesses.
His sister-in-law
and sister?
Although it's not a proper method,
Lord Zhou keeps urging me to release him.
I'm afraid I can't delay it for too long.
Lord Zhou
wants you to release him?
He doesn't want me to continue investigating the assassins.
In that case.
Sister, why don't you have that idler's sister-in-law and sister
stay at the Zhao Mansion?
After all, they are not real criminals,
and they are two women.
Staying in the Zhao Mansion
is also safe.
That's a good idea.
You are so smart, Han.
Zhu Zitong.
From today on.
I want you to assist Bingjingwu in investigating the case of the assassin and rebel.
These are your clothes.
I am just a commoner.
My abilities are limited.
What kind of ability do I have
to help you solve the case?
I am fully aware
of your abilities.
If you succeed,
I will naturally help you find
your long-lost daughter.
If you can help me find my daughter, sir,
I, Zhu Zitong,
will certainly do my best.
My Lord.
Liu Heizi has confessed.
There is new information.
My Lord is handling a case.
Wait here quietly.
Do not leave.
Not so stubborn anymore?
Please spare my life, My Lord.
Then confess honestly.
What's in your arms?
The assassin,
the meeting time,
and the meeting place.
Who wrote this secret message?
It's written in such detail.
This letter
is poisoned.
What's wrong with you?
My Lord.
Capital Commander Chu has repeatedly disobeyed Lord Zhou's orders.
He really is in league with those thieves.
My Lord.
Our Capital Commander
would never collude with thieves.
Please do not jump to conclusions, My Lord.
There must be some misunderstanding here.
Please investigate thoroughly, My Lord.
How dare you
question Lord Zhou.
Aren't you afraid
of losing your heads?
Calm down, my lord.
Perhaps there is
a misunderstanding here.
We will investigate immediately.
Then look into it right away.
I will watch right here,
so I can report back to Lord Zhou.
What does you being a rebel
have to do with our lord?
I contacted
Director Chu
in secret
to assassinate the Emperor.